A Royal Kick In The Arse
Shanghai Knights is a action, adventure, comedy film directed by David Dobkin.
When a Chinese rebel murders Chon's estranged father and escapes to England,
Chon and Roy make their way to London with revenge on their minds.
Chon Wang, played by Jackie Chan.
Roy O'Bannon, played by Owen Wilson.
Chon Lin, played by Fann Wong.
Lord Nelson Rathbone, played by Aidan Gillen.
Wu Chow, played by Donnie Yen.
Arthur 'Artie' Doyle, played by Tom Fisher.
Shanghai Knights is a 2003 martial arts western action comedy film.
It is the sequel to Shanghai Noon, and the second
installment of the Shanghai film series.
Directed by David Dobkin and written by Alfred Gough and Miles Millar, it stars
Jackie Chan, Owen Wilson, Fann Wong, Donnie Yen and Aidan Gillen.
It was released in the United States on February 7, 2003.
The film received mixed reviews but it performed well at the box office.
The film explores themes of martial arts, london,
england, indian territory, emperor, revenge.
The tone is lighthearted.